Roseph Darl Tungul

Web Developer | Instructor



About

I'm a freelance Web Developer and a parttime Instructor in the Philippines, with over 4 years of experience. I create and design one-of-a-kind websites and applications that aren't found in a template.

Contact

(+63-9281430222



(M) rosephdarl@gmail.com



(https://rdtungul.github.io/



(**9**) 99 San Nicolas 1st, Sasmuan, Pampanga, Philippines

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

 HTML5, CSS3/SCSS, PHP, JavaScript/ES6, Python, Node.js MySQL, MongoDB, Git, etc.

Frameworks/ Plugins:

 React, WebPack, Bootstrap 5, WordPress, Gutenberg, Elementor Pro, Shopify, ACF Pro, Astra Pro, WooCommerce, etc.

Softwares:

 Kajabi, WebFlow, Adobe XD, Figma, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Premiere Pro, FileZilla, Airtable, Asana, ConceptBoard, etc.

Education

(2015-2018) - Bachelor's Degree

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

(2019-2020) - Methods of Teaching

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Bachelor of Science in Secondary Education

(2020 - Present)

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Master in Business Administration

Experiences

(Oct. 2017 - Jan. 2018)

Beepo, Inc.

WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER / VIDEO EDITOR

(Apr. 2021 - Sept. 2021)

Pegasaas - Victoria, BC, Canada

TECHNICAL SUPPORT

(Jan. 2022 - Aug. 2022)

EasyWeb Leads - Sydney, Australia

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

(May 2018 - Present)

Guagua National Colleges

INSTRUCTOR

Websites that I've involved in both Front-end/ Backend Development:

- https://talostone.com.au/
- https://edenlaserclinics.com.au/
- waterlessurinalcartridges.com.au
- https://needmorestorage.com.au/
- https://cabinetsexpress.com.au/
- http://envirotech.com.au/
- https://www.cresi.ca/
- https://anna.asn.au/
- http://gnc.edu.ph/